Hello Hello Friends Welcome to LINK Stock
Market So today we are going to talk
about ICICI General Insurance
and are going to do a strong glass of it
for 11th April Twenty20 Let's fly straight to
our shots So this chart has been opened,
I have opened this chart in my account,
if you do
not have it then you can definitely subscribe in the description below and you can definitely
subscribe from there So as you can see
here I have
talked about
what support zone and research is formed in the stock for your Monday, I will
definitely tell you here
and here on today's launching a
basis what does Starc keep us
here, what can happen on the market day, I will definitely
give our confidential So let's get up and
see our ODI's sixth more there,
what is going to be seen in the stock in the coming days, so
here the shutter of ODI has already been
opened, if I talk about the
volume here then you
can see here anyway it is less here today, that
means building is going to be seen on Friday  There is
also a candle, which is
present here, in the acid
suicide on the downside, a biological is seen at both times.
Later, if I do RS
or RS 60 here, it gives us an
indication of the next moment here, but
remember, whether it is RS or Gaur indicator, we
cannot rely on shifted. There are
many updates here,
which should be done by giving this moment at any time,
whenever we
add any fennel peas. Now, as for
this rock of Parmesan, based on today's people
here for Monday, for that I will
definitely talk in the chart created,
but we will talk in the chart of ODI for the
coming days, their country,
in the upcoming general strike, we can definitely see a down
video because here right
now the app rock body is off side, but the
twenty makers are not at all needed for support here, so
because of that, we can
see a fall back to the rock around 3020, which means currently on Friday
crossing, there is a put of six points here to the
side.  In the coming days, it will be
seen that you should work a little, so that the stock does not reach here, the rest of the problem is definitely that the trend has become positive, it has crossed 2009, regarding female, here on Monday, just object, we must watch that, rest
what can happen in the stock in the coming days, do
tell us by commenting,
why do you think that this can happen, do tell that too,
but if you have not already subscribed to our channel, then
I will definitely
recommend you to subscribe to our channel,
here we
bring videos for all of you every day and videos that is, by adding them with four stroke, where we
tell you all how this is going to be available
from now or is going to be available again
and in the coming days,
definitely subscribe here, see here we bring every
day and here if you have
subscribed, then like the video here
and we
talk to us here, so
here first of all
I definitely tell someone else here, in the way
here I am asking you about my favorite  And
mark all these points
which will help you
in maintaining your target and stop loss, so
definitely when we do this here, for now,
if you have
not seen the video of our candidate yet, then I would
definitely recommend you to watch the video of our candidate, there are
many
important things here, you can
see this candlestick pattern and that will
help us in clearing our target and
stop loss, that is, in making a good decision here, whether it is
for the other side or for the other side, and
here right now the junior
research has taken all the responsibility of it
and here now let's talk about its closing in a
little bit, let me
see the data of both the sides, like this, so
here around 3090,
close war, direct support, here the
monkey director S of 3073, here 3293,
so remember the direct sports
director area is not
reading area, it means in the meantime if
you get to see in that half an hour, then here
you will definitely  You don't have to trend either. What you have to do is wait for the
stars to cross on either side and then,
looking at the confirmation rally, you have to take
your position here. If you don't know
what a confirmation candle is, then in the come button,
I have added the video on Concept and Targeted
Strategy here. When you
watch that video, I have
shown you the confirmation channel of this snake, how
you have to move ahead by finding all the problems and also
intraday, whether our stock goes down or from
above,
I have also explained to you how you can make profit in intraday, so
definitely watch this video
completely. Now,
my friend, before doing this, I will tell you
two important supports and two registers, here
also there are two supports, you can also make direct support direction, so
here the
direction is of 60
times, after the direction here the trough is of
939, after that the maximum is of 3097, so the
two supports that I have
told you here, definitely keep that in mind.
Here, our Monday is
appointed here, I definitely
mean here, I think
then here we will take it, it can be
found in between here 3333, but here the
subscribe can be kept on the side, so
below, I mean, you should try tempered glass, I am
not going to come, let me tell you,
currently, some time England, here on the
negative side, what do you think,
what can happen on Monday in this disease, do
tell us by commenting and if you
like our and nice, then please
like, share our video and do
not forget to subscribe to our channel, thank you
ki a ki
a